softarama.com 2012-12-29

# Softarama - The web's leading PC tune up utilities

Last updated 16 October 2010

This policy sets out Softarama LTD privacy practices in connection with all of the products & services offered by Softarama (collectively, "services"). If you wish to ask questions about this policy, or concerned about the way personal data is being handled by Softarama, or if you wish to get a copy of any personal data which you may have submitted to Softarama, please contact us or call us directly to +972-72-272-3804 or +972-72-272-3805.

## General statement

Softarama Ltd respects your right to privacy, and will not collect any personal information about you without your a clear and direct permission. Any personal information which you volunteer to Softarama will be treated with the appropriate standards of security and confidentiality, strictly in accordance with the Data Protection Acts, 1988 & 2003.

## Collection and use of personal information

Softarama does not and will not collect any personal data about you on our website or in connection with any other service, apart from information which you volunteer such as by e-mailing us, purchasing a product from us, downloading a product from us, or by registering your product with us, or by using our online forms. When you purchase a product from Softarama, we may collect information including your contact details. Please note that credit card information may be retained by our authorized billing provider as a record of any transaction we undertake with you. Information which you provide is used by Softarama only in line with the exact purpose for which you provided it and will not be made available to third parties under any circumstances, other than information provided to us during the purchase process which may be provided to our authorized billing provider for processing needs only. 

In case Softarama has your electronic mail address, we may contact you via email to advise you of product updates or offer you third party products once in a while. You can opt out from receiving these emails at any time. 

## Your rights regarding data supplied to Softarama

You have a right to be given a copy of any personal data which you may have supplied to Softarama in connection with any service. To exercise this right, contact us through our website or call us directly at: +972-72-272-3804 or +972-72-272-3805. If you are contacting us by email, you should include any personal identifiers which you supplied earlier (e.g. name, address, phone number, e-mail address). Your request will be dealt with as soon as possible and will take not more than 14 days to process.  
If you are concerned about how personal data is processed by Softarama, please do not hesitate to contact us directly.

## Collection and use of technical information

This website uses cookies: these are small files containing a string of characters that are sent to your computer to identify your browser - including temporary "session" cookies which enable a visitor's web browser to remember which pages on this website have already been visited and to track any referrer or affiliate information. Visitors can use this website with no substantial loss of functionality if cookies are disabled from the web browser.

Technical details in connection with visits to our website and our products may be logged by us or a third party for our statistical purposes and may also be used by our online billing provider to determine the purchase price during the purchase process. No information (apart from product purchase information) is collected that could be used by us to identify website visitors. The technical details logged are confined to the following types of information: 

• the Internet Protocol address or gateway of the visitor's web server   
• the previous website address from which the visitor reached us   
• clickstream data which shows the traffic of visitors around this web site (for example pages accessed and documents downloaded)   
• the type of web browser used by the visitor   
• the operating system of the visitor's computer   
• the screen resolution of the visitor's computer monitor   
• information on potential security risks, URLs of websites visited that Softarama deems potentially fraudulent and portable executable files that are identified as potential malware   
• information regarding installation of Softarama applications and other general, statistical information used for license administration, product analysis, and for improving product functionality. 

By supplementing our records, this information helps us learn things like: whether installation of our software was successfully completed; what pages are most attractive to our visitors; which of our products most interest our customers; what kinds of offers our customers like to see; evaluating and improving the ability of our products to detect malicious behavior, potentially fraudulent websites and other internet security risks and how to improve the ability of our products to detect malicious behavior. Where a third party logs information on our behalf, we control how that data may and may not be used. Softarama will make no attempt to identify individual visitors, or to associate the technical details listed above with any individual. It is our strict policy not to disclose such technical information in respect of individual website visitors to any third party (apart from any third party providing services to us which may record, process or analyze such data on our behalf and which is bound by confidentiality provisions in this regard), unless obliged or permitted to disclose such information by a rule of law.

The technical information will be used only by Softarama, and only for statistical and other administrative purposes. You should note that technical details, which we cannot associate with any identifiable individual, do not constitute "personal data" for the purposes of the Data Protection Acts, 1988 & 2003.

## Other websites

Softarama is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other websites accessible from this website via external links. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. Any external links to other websites are clearly identifiable as such.

## Changes to this policy

Please note that Softarama may change this policy from time to time. Any amended policy terms will be posted to the Softarama website – under the "News" section.

Microsoft, Windows, Windows logo, Internet Explorer, Internet Explorer logo are trademarks of the Microsoft group of companies. This site is not affiliated in any way, nor has it been authorized, sponsored, or otherwise approved by Microsoft Corporation.
